/*jshint esversion: 6 */

// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
const questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "When a killer shark unleashes chaos on a beach community, it's up to a local sheriff, a marine biologist, and an old seafarer to hunt the beast down.",
        answer: "Jaws",
        options: [
            "Casablanca",
            "The Terminator",
            "Jaws",
            "The Bad Seed"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "An in-depth examination of the ways in which the U.S. Vietnam War impacts and disrupts the lives of people in a small industrial town in Pennsylvania.",
        answer: "The Deer Hunter",
        options: [
            "The Deer Hunter",
            "Rain Man" ,
            "Logan's Run",
            "A Star is Born"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The presidencies of Kennedy and Johnson, the events of Vietnam, Watergate, and other history unfold through the perspective of an Alabama man with an IQ of 75.",
        answer: "Forrest Gump",
        options: [ 
            "The Shining",
            "Jurassic Park",
            "Rear Window",
            "Forrest Gump"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Two imprisoned men bond over a number of years, finding solace and eventual redemption through acts of common decency.",
        answer: "The Shawshank Redemption",
        options: [
            "The Shawshank Redemption",
            "The Good, The Bad and The Ugly",
            "The Godfather",
            "North by Northwest"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "A Polish Jewish musician struggles to survive the destruction of the Warsaw ghetto of World War II.",
        answer: "The Pianist",
        options: [
            "Schindler's List",
            "The Pianist",
            "Citizen Kane",
            "Breakfast at Tiffany's"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Dictator Adenoid Hynkel tries to expand his empire while a poor Jewish barber tries to avoid persecution from Hynkel's regime.",
        answer: "The Great Dictator",
        options: [
            "A Star is Born",
            "Psycho",
            "Rocky",
            "The Great Dictator"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:  "Atticus Finch, a lawyer in the Depression-era South, defends a black man against an undeserved rape charge, and his children against prejudice.",
        answer: "To Kill a Mockingbird",
        options: [
            "To Kill a Mockingbird",
            "Brief Encounter",
            "It's a Wonderful Life",
            "My Fair Lady"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "A jury holdout attempts to prevent a miscarriage of justice by forcing his colleagues to reconsider the evidence",
        answer: "Twelve Angry Men",
        options: [
            "West Side Story",
            "The Third Man",
            "Die Hard",
            "Twelve Angry Men"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "A manipulative woman and a roguish man conduct a turbulent romance during the American Civil War and Reconstruction periods",
        answer: "Gone with the Wind",
        options: [
            "Ben-Hur",
            "Sunset Boulevard",
            "Gone with the Wind",
            "The Deer Hunter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "A criminal pleads insanity after getting into trouble again and once in the mental institution rebels against the oppressive nurse and rallies up the scared patients.",
        answer: "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest",
        options: [
            "The Princess Bride",
            "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest",
            "Forrest Gump",
            "My Fair Lady"
        ]
    }
]